[{"id": "22ERT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which of these languages does not use a semi-colon?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["Java", "Perl", "Python", "C++"], "answers": ["Python"], "score": "5", "explanation": "The correct answer is Python, Python is the only language among these choices that do not use semi-colon", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "21ERT", "module": "Fintech", "question": "Fintech is revolutionary", "question_type": "TF", "choices": ["True", "False"], "answers": ["True"], "score": "5", "explanation": "The correct answer is True, isn't that obvious? :)", "answered_count": 0}, {"id": "22DDT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which of these are programming languages?", "question_type": "MCQ", "choices": ["Python", "Cantonese", "Ruby", "R"], "answers": ["Python", "Ruby", "R"], "score": "20", "explanation": "The correct answers are Python, Ruby and R. Cantonese is a form of Chinese spoken by over 54 million people, mainly in south-eastern China (including Hong Kong)", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "22OOT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "How do you iterate an array in Javascript?", "question_type": "MCQ", "choices": ["array.find()", "array.substring()", "array.filter()", "array.map()"], "answers": ["array.map()", "array.find()", "array.filter()"], "score": "20", "explanation": "all except 'array.substring()' iterate an array. 'array.substring' takes all or number of characters in a string", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "22ERQ", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Tkinter is a programming language", "question_type": "TF", "choices": ["True", "False"], "answers": ["False"], "score": "5", "explanation": "The correct answer is False. Tkinter is a module in Python", "answered_count": 4}, {"id": "22ER1", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which is not a field in computer science?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["Software development", "Embedded Systems", "Artificial Intelligence", "Fintech"], "answers": ["Fintech"], "score": "10", "explanation": "Fintech is the correct answer, it falls under banking & finance", "answered_count": 1}, {"id": "20QRT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Select all that are closely related", "question_type": "MCQ", "choices": ["Xamarin", "React Native", "Flutter", "Laravel"], "answers": ["Xamarin", "React Native", "Flutter"], "score": "10", "explanation": "All except Laravel are cross-platform frameworks for mobile application development, Laravel is a framework of PHP, a server side language", "answered_count": 2}, {"id": "FVP0F", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Select the ones that don't apply", "question_type": "MCQ", "choices": ["Laravel", "Symphony", "Yii", "Codename one"], "answers": ["Codename one"], "score": "10", "explanation": "Codename one is a cross-platform framework of Java/Kotlin for mobile app development, all others are frameworks of PHP", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "20CRT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which role in software development exposes API and handles request to the database?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["Frontend", "Backend", "Devops", "UI/UX"], "answers": ["Backend"], "score": "5", "explanation": "Backend is the correct answer", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "22EVV", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Python is written in?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["C", "F", "Java", "Python"], "answers": ["C"], "score": "5", "explanation": "The correct answer is C programming language", "answered_count": 4}, {"id": "22190", "module": "CSC01", "question": "How do you destructure an object in Javascript?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["const value = object.value", "const [a, b] = object", "const {a, b} = object", "object = {...a, b}"], "answers": ["const {a, b} = object"], "score": "5", "explanation": "const {a, b} = object is the correct answer, read about 'destructuring in javascript'", "answered_count": 5}, {"id": "89YRT", "module": "CSC01", "question": "How do you make a base class inherit properties of a parent class in Python?", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["class Question(Home):", "class Question extends Home:", "class Question inherits Home:", "class Question[Home]:"], "answers": ["class Question(Home):"], "score": "10", "explanation": "class Question(Home): is the correct answer", "answered_count": 5}, {"id": "IHFPM", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which of this is not a valid data type in python", "question_type": "BM", "choices": ["array", "string", "dictionary", "list"], "answers": ["array"], "score": "10", "explanation": "array is a data type in javascript and a couple of other languages", "answered_count": 6}, {"id": "1YQUS", "module": "CSC01", "question": "Which of these are not data types in javascript?", "question_type": "MCQ", "choices": ["list", "array", "object", "string"], "answers": ["list"], "score": "15", "explanation": "list is a data type in python, all other data types are valid", "answered_count": 3}, {"id": "KBBIK", "module": "BUS", "question": "Business is about making money", "question_type": "TF", "choices": ["True", "False"], "answers": ["True"], "score": "2", "explanation": "LOL, come on", "answered_count": 0}, {"id": "F8MVE", "module": "BUS", "question": "\"Break even\" is to reach a point where profit is equal to capital", "question_type": "TF", "choices": ["True", "False"], "answers": ["False"], "score": "5", "explanation": "\"Break even\" is to reach a point where profit is equal to COST, not capital", "answered_count": 0}]